### PERSONAL FEED

I have a Software Engineering degree from Universidad de Colima, My working experience runs around ruby on rails, react JS.

My professional career started at Bright Coders Academy, with a successful course on Ruby on Rails, a few months after I began working at MagmaLabs.

My actual role is RoR dev on MagmaLabs and mentoring at BrightCoders Academy. I'm part of the Playas on tech community in Manzanillo and enjoy my time creating content and code for my personal brand.



### CONTACT



(314) - 142 -28 - 86



🔽 ramon.g.uz37@gmail.com



Juanequex.github.io



Manzanillo, Colima



### $oxedsymbol{oxed}$ HARD SKILLS

- Javascript
- HTML/SASS
- React JS
- Ruby On Rails
- Ruby
- Git / Github
- Figma
- Mentoring

## SOFT SKILLS

- Adaptability
- Team Working
- Conflict Resolution
- Cre ativity
- Retention of customer requirements
- Conflict Resolution



## (#) ENGLISH LEVEL

**495 TOEFL SCORE** 

# JUAN R. GUZMAN AGUILAR

### SOFTWARE ENGINEER



## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### **MAGMALABS FEB 2022 - CURRENT**

### SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Currently, I Develop On Technologies Such As Ruby On Rails And React In Very Diverse Projects Within The MagmaLabs Client Portfolio And In Its Internal Projects

#### **BRIGHTCODERS MENTOR FEB 2022 - CURRENT**

#### **MENTOR**

I've Been Distinguished As a Mentor With The Responsabilite To Share Best Practices Of Coding And Support In The Development Of BrightCoders Participants.

- Evidence 1
- Evicence 2



## CERTIFICATIONS

### **BRIGHTCODERS ACADEMY AGO 2021 - DIC 2021**

#### PROJECT INTERN

I was part of a trainee program in which, together with a team of developers, we received training on Ruby / Ruby on Rails, Git and Github, Agile methodology, and teamwork. We solved different challenges and developed a web project together

Evidence



## GIVING BACK

### PLAYAS ON TECH AGO 2022 - CURRENT

#### COMMUNITY ORGANIZER

I'm a member of the organizing committee of the project.

Community Site



## **EDUCATION**

#### **UNIVERSIDAD DE COLIMA 2018 - 2022**

Software Engineering at Faculty Of **Telematics**